<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>This is a blog.</title>
    <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on This is a blog.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krokodyl.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WaiWai Check 03/21 (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-check-3-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-check-3-21/</guid>
      <description>Waiwai Check 3/21 (わいわいチェック 3/21) is a Satellaview game.
The ROM was originally dumped through the effort of several people and published on the Satellablog.
As the game was packed together with another one, I took the liberty to extract the game and rebuild a working pack with the game alone.
Roms (Japanese and English) Japanese ROM English ROM Download WaiWai Check 3-21 (Japanese).bs Download WaiWai Check 3-21 (English).bs The game The game is a &amp;ldquo;spot the difference&amp;rdquo; game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WaiWai Check 11/15 (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-check-11-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-check-11-15/</guid>
      <description>WaiWai Check 11/15 Rerun (わいわいチェック 11/15 再放送) is a Satellaview game.
The ROM was originally dumped through the effort of several people and published on the Satellablog.
Roms (Japanese and English) Japanese ROM English ROM Download WaiWai Check 11-15 (Japanese).bs Download WaiWai Check 11-15 (English).bs The game The game is a &amp;ldquo;spot the difference&amp;rdquo; game.
You have an animated image on the left and the mirrored version on the right with 5 differences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuki no WaiWai Kids (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-kids/</guid>
      <description>Yuki no WaiWai Kids 3/16 (有紀のワイワイKIDS 3/16) is a Satellaview game.
The ROM was originally dumped through the effort of several people and published on the Satellablog.
As the game was packed together with another one, I took the liberty to extract the game and rebuild a working pack with the game alone.
Roms (Japanese and English) Japanese ROM English ROM Download WaiWai Kids 3-16 (Japanese).bs Download WaiWai Kids 3-16 (English).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Koi wa Balance (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/koi-wa-balance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/koi-wa-balance/</guid>
      <description>English translation for the 1996 Satellaview (an extension of the Super Famicom/Super Nintendo only released in Japan) game Koi wa Balance: Tatoeba K-kun no Tabou na Ichinichi Hen. The Japanese title (恋はバランス たとえばK君の多忙な一日編) roughly translates to &amp;ldquo;Love is balance - for example, K&amp;rsquo;s busy day&amp;rdquo;.
Sometimes referred as Koi ha Balance - Battle of Lovers (は is ha when out of context but read as wa as a particle).
This is a party game for up to 4 players in which you play as one of four brothers who are competing in a challenge set up by their dying grand-father, head of the family business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dokapon Gaiden (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-gaiden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-gaiden/</guid>
      <description>This is the English translation of the Super Famicom (SNES) videogame: ドカポン外伝 〜炎のオーディション～ Dokapon Gaiden 〜Honō no Audition〜
The 3rd game in the Dokapon series.
外伝 (gaiden) means &amp;lsquo;Side Story&amp;rsquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s often used in fiction for work that references previous one while not being a direct sequel.
Game 4 players (Human or CPUs) take turns going around a board. The goal is to have the most gold at the end.You get gold from different sources: random events, fighting monsters, fighting other players (you take half of the gold of defeated opponents) or simply completing a lap around the board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kessen! Dokapon Kingdom IV (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/kessen-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/kessen-translation/</guid>
      <description>English fan translation for the SNES game
Kessen! Dokapon Oukoku IV - Densetsu no Yuusha-tachi.
The Japanese title (決戦! ドカポン王国 (ランド) IV ~伝説の勇者たち~) roughly translates to &amp;ldquo;Decisive Battle! Dokapon Kingdoms IV: Legendary Heroes&amp;rdquo;.
This is the very first game in the Dokapon game series. The IV in the title refers to the possibility of supporting up to 4 players and was probably also mocking the numbering of JRPG that was getting out of hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dokapon 3-2-1 Wiki</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-3-2-1-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-3-2-1-wiki/</guid>
      <description>This is a single page version of the wiki I made on github (link).
Content Game Modes Jobs Combat System Spaces Training Area Equipment Items Magic Status Towns Map Special-Events Memory-Cheats Game modes Normal mode Whoever collects the most assets (gold + towns) in a set period of time wins.
The period can be selected from 1 to 9999 weeks, and can be changed even during the game.
In this mode, you can choose the character level at the start and the initial equipment will change accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dokapon 3-2-1 (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-3-2-1-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-3-2-1-translation/</guid>
      <description>This project is a fan translation file of the Super Famicom video game
Dokapon 3-2-1: Arashi o Yobu Yuujou (ドカポン3・2・1 〜嵐を呼ぶ友情〜) released in 1994.
Dokapon 3-2-1 is the second Dokapon game for the Super Famicom. Like its predecessor, it follows a group of ragtag RPG heroes across a board game-like map as they attempt to outmaneuver each other and be the first to save the kingdom. Characters move around determinant on dice rolls and can acquire items and treasure depending on where they land.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
