<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>This is a blog.</title>
    <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content on This is a blog.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krokodyl.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dynami Tracer Quiz</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/08/dynami-tracer-quiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/08/dynami-tracer-quiz/</guid>
      <description>Normal Quiz - Questions and Answers ⚠ All answers must be typed in uppercase!
ID Question Answer 19 No idea what they are but their ride is a mysterious fish. They&amp;rsquo;re contestant #6. What is Jim&amp;rsquo;s name? TASOGARENO 1A The Mitsutomo Galaxy Company is hosting this Dynami Trace. What is Mr. Mitsutomo&amp;rsquo;s first name? KONOSUKE 1B What is the name of the vehicle of contestant #2, Rose Tetsuwan? MACH MARY 1C He&amp;rsquo;s a very quiet bearded man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynami Tracer Treasure List</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/08/dynami-tracer-treasures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/08/dynami-tracer-treasures/</guid>
      <description>Planets Adults Clockwork Star Minimum Star Monster Stomach Octave (Music) Sand Planet Satella (Station) Skull Bone Twin Star
Adults (アダルツ) Id Name Pts Location 4D ブロマイドNaga Bromide 1 From the old man in the audience Clockwork Star (クロックワークスター) Id Name Pts Location 01 ブルーストーンBlue Stone 7 Chest in town (block 7) 15 タキシードTuxedo 5 Chest in town (block 3) 1A レディスーツPantsuit 5 Chest in town (block 4) 46 ビップカードVIP Card 100 Help everyone in town and stop the time loop 5F ガラスのゆびわGlass Ring 3 Talk to the birthday boy after breaking the time machine 60 おとめのなみだYoung Girl Tears 73 Do not spoil the TV drama ending for the girl 61 100まんギル1 Million Gils 1 Pick the lottery ticket with 9281616 62 ネコまっしぐら9 out of 10 cats 57 Rescue the cat in the well in Block 3 at 6 pm 63 ななつどうぐBasic Tool Set 60 Catch the thief in block 9 at 9pm then in block 1 64 しろいめがみぞうGoddess Figurine 111 Pray to the Goddess and let the old woman win the lottery 65 ホカホカやきいもHot Baked Potato 5 Warn the man by the bonfire before 12 pm 66 いちわりのおれい10% off coupon 10 Check the bin in block 5 at 11 am 67 にわりのおれい20% off coupon 20 Check the bin in block 7 at 4 pm 68 プラチナチケットPlatinum Ticket 10 Tell the man to bet on the Dudgers 69 ふたりのきもちMutual Feelings 22 Find the girlfriend in the morning after talking to the boyfriend in the afternoon (block 2) 6A マドーのとけいMadow&amp;rsquo;s Watch 1 Chest in town 6B タイムマシンネジTime Machine Rod 100 In Madow&amp;rsquo;s lab Minimum Star (ミニマムスター) Id Name Pts Location 6D おうごんのはかGolden Tombstone 100 70 おうごんのとうGolden Spire 100 71 おうごんのビルGolden Building 100 73 きんのおやしきGolden Mansion 100 76 おうごんのいえGolden House 100 77 ゴールデンハウスGolden Pagoda 100 78 ゴールデンタワーGolden Tower 100 79 くつについたきんGolden Shoe 30 Monster Stomach (モンスター・ストマック) Id Name Pts Location 03 グリーンストーンGreen Stone 7 Defend the bacteria (far north room) 07 カルトのあかしCult Certificate 0 Beat the Cult Quiz (bottom middle room) 09 げんじのこてGenji Gauntlet 50 Mastermind game (bottom left room) 0B クリスタルメットCrystal Helmet 50 Mastermind game (bottom left room) 14 ステッキCane 5 Odd one out game (bottom right room) 19 ハイヒールHigh Heels 5 Find the lying bacteria (north room) 2A リボンRibbon 150 The opposite answers challenge (west room) 2E みずのクリスタルWater Crystal 250 3E きんのはりGold Needle 52 Win the Three-card monte (east room) 47 コッペリアCoppelia 200 Complete all the rooms 48 バクルドのきもちBactroy&amp;rsquo;s Joy 1 Saved from the quiz 49 バクティのこころBacterry&amp;rsquo;s Heart 11 Saved from the quiz 4A バクースのたからBactus&amp;rsquo; Treasure 111 Saved from the quiz 50 マヨネーのブラFlea Vest 100 The opposite answers challenge (west room) 7F ジムのメダルJim&amp;rsquo;s Medal 1 Win the Three-card monte (east room) Octave (オクターブ) Id Name Pts Location 39 あいのフライパンFry Pan of Love 8 Say yes to the folk singer in the karaoke lobby 3B エリクサーElixir 100 On the race track 41 まもりのゆびわProtect Ring 100 On the race track 58 きんのモズしょうGold Shrike Award 100 Theme song race: 8+ checkpoints 1st 59 ぎんのモズしょうSilver Shrike Award 78 Theme song race: 4-7 checkpoints 1st 5A どうのモズしょうBronze Shrike Award 53 Theme song race: 1-3 checkpoints 1st 5B えんかのこころEnka&amp;rsquo;s Essence 25 Given by Sabugorō after the race if one enka line is in the song 5C ロックのシャウトRock Screaming 25 Given by Ebis after the race if one rock line is in the song 5D ヒーローファイトHero&amp;rsquo;s Spirit 25 Given by Utauda after the race one hero line is in the song 5E アイドルのフリルIdol&amp;rsquo;s Frill 25 Given by Kuriko after the race if one idol line is in the song Sand Planet (サンドプラネット) Id Name Pts Location 00 レッドストーンRed Stone 7 Moleman&amp;rsquo;s cave 08 げんじのかぶとGenji Helmet 50 0C クリスタルのこてCrystal Gauntlet 50 10 ミスリルメイルMythril Mail 25 1D ちょうはなふだButterflies Card 9 1E やくひんアルファCompound Alpha 15 22 エクスカリパーExcalipoor 1 Dig in the desert 23 バハムートエッグBahamut&amp;rsquo;s Egg 200 Dig in the desert 24 バカムートエッグBakamut&amp;rsquo;s Egg 1 25 つきのしずくMoondrop 108 2D つちのクリスタルEarth Crystal 250 30 ディフェンダーDefender 78 3D ギサールのやさいGysahl Greens 8 3F バッカスのさけBacchus&amp;rsquo;s Wine 87 40 さんごのつるぎCoral Sword 50 Dig in the desert 43 まんまるドロップCandy 10 44 ぱっくんチョコChocolate 15 45 ぎんのせいはいSilver Chalice 63 4B ドラゴンキラーDragon Killer 109 4C ドラゴソキラーDerguhn Killer 1 Dig in the desert 4E ビネガーパンツOzzie Pants 1 51 ヌゥのケNu&amp;rsquo;s Trace 50 Moleman&amp;rsquo;s cave 52 ドリストーンDreamstone 100 53 さわやかセットRefresher Set 20 Listen to both Moleman stories 54 しなやかセットChoice Set 40 55 すこやかセットHealthy Set 60 56 たおやかセットGraceful Set 80 57 にぎやかセットCheerful Set 100 6E コンピュータロムComputer ROM 3 6F さんかくおにぎりRice Ball 3 Dig in the desert 72 てっかめんIron Mask 4 Dig in the desert 74 すいせいのかけらMeteorite 9 Dig in the desert 75 ポヨぞーのひみつPoyozo&amp;rsquo;s Secret 100 Dig in the desert 7C アーリーのメダルEarly&amp;rsquo;s Medal 1 Satella (サテラ) Id Name Pts Location 04 オレンジストーンOrange Stone 7 1F - South hallway hidden room - locked chest 05 ホワイトストーンWhite Stone 7 1F - North East hallway hidden room - locked chest 0F ミスリルのこてMythril Gauntlet 25 Central room (2F) 13 シルクハットTop Hat 5 Central room (2F) 18 ルージュRouge 5 Central room (2F) 1B いのししはなふだBoar Card 9 Control room (1F) 20 ティンクルスターTwinkle Star 99 Central room (2F) 29 ピンクのしっぽPink Tail 69 Central room (Base Floor) 2B かくばくだんNuclear Weapon 74 Central room (Base Floor) 2F かぜのクリスタルWind Crystal 250 Control room (1F) 33 マサムネMasamune 100 Central room (Base Floor) 38 ファバードFirebird Card 96 Central room (Base Floor) 42 ラグナロクRagnarok 100 Central room (Base Floor) 6C マイクロディスクMicro-Disk 50 Control room (1F) 7B ローゼのメダルRose&amp;rsquo;s Medal 1 Control room (1F) Skull Bone (スカル・ボーン) Id Name Pts Location 06 ブラックストーンBlack Stone 7 Near the couple, bottom row, middle grave 0D クリスタルメイルCrystal Mail 50 1st lord grave 0E ミスリルかぶとMythril Helmet 25 Near the couple, top row, right grave 12 つけヒゲFake Mustache 5 Near the couple, top row, middle grave 17 あみタイツFishnet Tights 5 Rescue the bullied lady 1C しかはなふだDeer Card 9 Destroy grandma&amp;rsquo;s grave 1F やくひんベータCompound Beta 15 From the gandma with back pain 27 グランドリオンGrandleon 201 From the Death Metal barman after getting the fire crystal 2C ひのクリスタルFire Crystal 250 From Deathbone after doing all 5 good deeds 31 イージスのたてAegis Shield 120 4th lord grave 32 よいちのゆみやYoichi Bow 41 Encourage the girl on a date 34 スーパーエッグSuper Egg 56 Pick up the contact lenses 35 イビルエッグEvil Egg 56 3rd lord grave 3A ほうちょうKnife 100 Comfort the crying girl in the graveyard 7A ダニエルのメダルDaniel&amp;rsquo;s Medal 1 Comfort the crying girl in the graveyard 7E ワイルドのメダルWilde&amp;rsquo;s Medal 1 Cross the Death Metal stage Twin Star (ツインスター) Id Name Pts Location 02 イエローストーンYellow Stone 7 Blue Mouse castle treasure room 0A げんじのよろいGenji Armor 50 Blue Mouse castle treasure room 11 はなメガネPince-nez 5 Talk to the guards at the start of the race 16 むねパットBra Inserts 5 After winning the mouse race, in the small house (mouse) 21 オニオンソードOnion Sword 155 2nd floor chest 26 ぎんがねこのヒゲCat Whiskers 55 28 ネズミのしっぽRat Tail 90 After winning the mouse race, in the small house (chest) 36 ワンダーエッグWonder Egg 112 2nd floor chest 37 デッドガンDead Cannon Card 93 3rd floor chest 3C フェニックスのおPhoenix Down 100 After winning the mouse race, in the big house (chest) 4F ソイソーとうSlasher 50 Blue Mouse castle treasure room 7D ハーパーのメダルHarper&amp;rsquo;s Medal 1 Blue Mouse castle treasure room </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynami Tracer (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/08/dynami-tracer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/08/dynami-tracer/</guid>
      <description>Content The game English Patch Characters Vehicles Treasure list Planet Twin Star Planet Octave Planet Skull Bone Planet Adults Planet Clockwork Star Monster Stomach Normal Quiz Cult Quiz Satella Sand Planet Planet Minimum Star Credits
The game This is the last of 4 games developed by Squaresoft for the Satellaview, the extension of the Super Famicom (SNES). The other games being Radical Dreamers, Koi wa Balance and Treasure Conflix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordle for SNES (Satebo&#39;s Wordgame)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/satebo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/satebo/</guid>
      <description>Satebo&amp;rsquo;s Wordgame is a homebrew game for the Satellaview (the Super Famicom extension). It is an implementation of the Wordle game, developped by Josh Wardle, that became popular in 2021 before being bought by the New York Times.
The game is named after Satebo, one of the two Satellaview mascots. (Satebo: ) and Parabo: ) Why did you spell wordgame in one word? I don&amp;rsquo;t know, why is wargame spelled in one word?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to play Satellaview games on PC</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/how-to-satellaview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/how-to-satellaview/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisite Have a SNES emulator.
1. Download the Satellaview BIOS The file can be downloaded on the BS-X Project Blog
BS-X BIOS (English) [No DRM] [2016 v1.3].sfc I recommend taking the ENGLISH + NO DRM version.
2. Place the BIOS in your emulator config (optional) Some emulators automatically look for the BIOS in a specific folder or with a specific file name. Either way, you should keep it in a known location, as you&amp;rsquo;ll need it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Conflix (French)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/treasure-conflix-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/treasure-conflix-fr/</guid>
      <description>Traduction française du jeu Satellaview (SNES/Super Famicom) トレジャーコンフリクス (Treasure Conflix) sortie en 1996 par Squaresoft. Le jeu mélange des éléments de RPG avec des combats aériens en mode 7. Cependant, l&amp;rsquo;essentiel du jeu consiste à parler à des PNJ et à résoudre des énigmes pour trouver des trésors.
Conseils pour une première partie Utiliser L et R avec le D-pad pour tourner plus vite. On ne peut trouver un trésor qu&amp;rsquo;après avoir obtenu un indice ou une carte pour ce trésor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Conflix - All Treasure Locations</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/treasure-conflix-maps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/treasure-conflix-maps/</guid>
      <description>There are 32 treasures to find in the game (not counting the Cloud Gate, which is the main story element).
20 of the treasures are found with a clue given by an NPC.
8 of the treasures are found using a treasure map given by an NPC.
4 of the treasures are underwater in the Doom Triangle.
World Map Click here for world mapWorld Map Full Resolution (4096x4096)
Treasure Locations Amethyst Bracelet Click here for the treasure locationAncient Coin Click here for the treasure locationAncient Scriptures Click here for the treasure locationAngel&amp;rsquo;s Bow Click here for the treasure locationBlack Coral Hairpin Click here for the treasure locationCat&amp;rsquo;s Eye Click here for the treasure locationCursed Mirror Click here for the treasure locationDiamond Ring Click here for the treasure locationUnderwater in the Doom Triangle (Dark waters around the Salvage Ship)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treasure Conflix (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/treasure-conflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/treasure-conflix/</guid>
      <description>English translation for the Satellaview (SNES/Super Famicom) game トレジャーコンフリクス (Treasure Conflix) released in 1996 by Squaresoft. The game mixes RPG elements with some airship fights in mode 7. Most of the focus is on talking with NPCs and solving riddles trying to find the locations of treasures.
Tips for your first playthrough You can use L and R in conjunction with the D-pad to turn faster while in combat. You can only find a treasure after you&amp;rsquo;ve been given the clue or the map for that treasure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WaiWai Check 03/21 (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-check-3-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-check-3-21/</guid>
      <description>Waiwai Check 3/21 (わいわいチェック 3/21) is a Satellaview game.
The ROM was originally dumped through the effort of several people and published on the Satellablog.
As the game was packed together with another one, I took the liberty to extract the game and rebuild a working pack with the game alone.
Roms (Japanese and English) Japanese ROM English ROM Download WaiWai Check 3-21 (Japanese).bs Download WaiWai Check 3-21 (English).bs The game The game is a &amp;ldquo;spot the difference&amp;rdquo; game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WaiWai Check 11/15 (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-check-11-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-check-11-15/</guid>
      <description>WaiWai Check 11/15 Rerun (わいわいチェック 11/15 再放送) is a Satellaview game.
The ROM was originally dumped through the effort of several people and published on the Satellablog.
Roms (Japanese and English) Japanese ROM English ROM Download WaiWai Check 11-15 (Japanese).bs Download WaiWai Check 11-15 (English).bs The game The game is a &amp;ldquo;spot the difference&amp;rdquo; game.
You have an animated image on the left and the mirrored version on the right with 5 differences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuki no WaiWai Kids (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/waiwai-kids/</guid>
      <description>Yuki no WaiWai Kids 3/16 (有紀のワイワイKIDS 3/16) is a Satellaview game.
The ROM was originally dumped through the effort of several people and published on the Satellablog.
As the game was packed together with another one, I took the liberty to extract the game and rebuild a working pack with the game alone.
Roms (Japanese and English) Japanese ROM English ROM Download WaiWai Kids 3-16 (Japanese).bs Download WaiWai Kids 3-16 (English).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Koi wa Balance (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/koi-wa-balance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/koi-wa-balance/</guid>
      <description>English translation for the 1996 Satellaview (an extension of the Super Famicom/Super Nintendo only released in Japan) game Koi wa Balance: Tatoeba K-kun no Tabou na Ichinichi Hen. The Japanese title (恋はバランス たとえばK君の多忙な一日編) roughly translates to &amp;ldquo;Love is balance - for example, K&amp;rsquo;s busy day&amp;rdquo;.
Sometimes referred as Koi ha Balance - Battle of Lovers (は is ha when out of context but read as wa as a particle).
This is a party game for up to 4 players in which you play as one of four brothers who are competing in a challenge set up by their dying grand-father, head of the family business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dokapon Gaiden (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-gaiden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-gaiden/</guid>
      <description>This is the English translation of the Super Famicom (SNES) videogame: ドカポン外伝 〜炎のオーディション～ Dokapon Gaiden 〜Honō no Audition〜
The 3rd game in the Dokapon series.
外伝 (gaiden) means &amp;lsquo;Side Story&amp;rsquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s often used in fiction for work that references previous one while not being a direct sequel.
Game 4 players (Human or CPUs) take turns going around a board. The goal is to have the most gold at the end.You get gold from different sources: random events, fighting monsters, fighting other players (you take half of the gold of defeated opponents) or simply completing a lap around the board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kessen! Dokapon Kingdom IV (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/kessen-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/kessen-translation/</guid>
      <description>English fan translation for the SNES game
Kessen! Dokapon Oukoku IV - Densetsu no Yuusha-tachi.
The Japanese title (決戦! ドカポン王国 (ランド) IV ~伝説の勇者たち~) roughly translates to &amp;ldquo;Decisive Battle! Dokapon Kingdoms IV: Legendary Heroes&amp;rdquo;.
This is the very first game in the Dokapon game series. The IV in the title refers to the possibility of supporting up to 4 players and was probably also mocking the numbering of JRPG that was getting out of hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dokapon 3-2-1 Wiki</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-3-2-1-wiki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-3-2-1-wiki/</guid>
      <description>This is a single page version of the wiki I made on github (link).
Content Game Modes Jobs Combat System Spaces Training Area Equipment Items Magic Status Towns Map Special-Events Memory-Cheats Game modes Normal mode Whoever collects the most assets (gold + towns) in a set period of time wins.
The period can be selected from 1 to 9999 weeks, and can be changed even during the game.
In this mode, you can choose the character level at the start and the initial equipment will change accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dokapon 3-2-1 (English)</title>
      <link>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-3-2-1-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://krokodyl.github.io/post/2023/07/dokapon-3-2-1-translation/</guid>
      <description>This project is a fan translation file of the Super Famicom video game
Dokapon 3-2-1: Arashi o Yobu Yuujou (ドカポン3・2・1 〜嵐を呼ぶ友情〜) released in 1994.
Dokapon 3-2-1 is the second Dokapon game for the Super Famicom. Like its predecessor, it follows a group of ragtag RPG heroes across a board game-like map as they attempt to outmaneuver each other and be the first to save the kingdom. Characters move around determinant on dice rolls and can acquire items and treasure depending on where they land.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
